To be continued
I'm going to do it.
You're amazing, Ban-chan.
You're aiming for the edge.
Thank you for watching. Please
subscribe to our channel.
Ban-chan is the youngest member.
I don't think she can beat her.
I was impressed by her performance at
the spring tour.
Her voice is so good.
I want to go to her concert.
Please let me go.
Please.
The next match is Bambi vs. Oharu.
The winner will compete with each
other.
1 vs 1.
Come on!
Haru-san is fighting with her juniors.
I can't lose to younger girls.
I'll do my best.
Ready, go!
I don't think I can beat Ban-chan.
Ban-chan vs Haru-chan
To be continued.
Wow!
It's a bungee jump!
I'll do it.
No!
Bungee jump.
I'll do it.
Wow!
You did it!
I did it!
I can't do it?
I'll do it.
Oharu!
Oh!
I didn't know what to say.
Oharu is catching the ball.
I can't catch it.
Wow!
Oharu is great!
It's 4 to 2.
Yes!
Wow!
Amazing!
It's amazing!
Oh, nice!
No!
Bambi!
It's a good game, isn't it?
It's fast!
4 to 5
Bambi caught up with the ball.
Which one was it?
It was Bambi.
She caught up with the ball.
It's a tie.
6 points.
Amazing.
Next.
I think it's Haru.
It's a tie.
Oh!
Bambi!
Extended line!
Wow!
Let's go!
Stack up!
Hey!
Oh!
Wow!
Fua!
Oh!
Bambi is barely...
Fua!
Oh!
Oh, wait!
It's a two-point difference!
Oh!
I hate it.
I'll go!
Fua!
Bambi!
You're good at this!
Here I go!
Bambi!
Bambi is the match point.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Wow! You're really good at it!
Let's go!
The game is over!
I'm so happy!
Thank you for watching! Please
subscribe to my channel!
Oh!
Oharu-chan!
Wow!
This is good.
Wow! I did two bounces!
Two times!
Haru and Oharu-chan!
Let's go!
Wall! Wall!
You're amazing, Ban-chan!
That was close!
You're really aiming for the edge.
Yeah, I am.
You're going to get hit again!
Just end it already!
Here I go.
Bambi.
Bambi is the match point.
I'm going to win.
What was that?
Sassy
I can't believe it!
Bambi is waiting for the ball.
Bambi wins!
Wow!
That was amazing.
15 to 17.
That was a great match.
Please subscribe to this channel!
Julia? I don't know about her.
I think she is elegant.
She uses ballet techniques.
So I think she is hip-hop.
Yo! Yo!
I think she is...
I've never competed with her.
I've never said, I can't do it.
So I think she can't do it.
Is she strong?
I wonder.
She is strong.
She is doing it.
I think she can do it.
I'll do my best.
This is the battle between the losers.
Don't say that.
I lost to Man-chan.
So I'll win this time.
I changed the racket.
I'll do my best.
I won't lose to Miss Elegant.
What?
Ready, go!
No!
What's going on?
It's Juri.
Here I go.
Oh no.
What? Something's coming!
I'm scared!
Here I go.
Okay.
What?
I'm scared!
The ball's fast.
It's not fast.
Wait!
Wow.
Okay.
Juri's turn.
Practiceumes
Ah!
Oh, thank you.
Ready, go!
Go!
Ah!
I did it!
It's Julia.
Oh!
Julia!
You're fast!
You're beautiful.
Ready, go!
Go!
Ah!
I did it!
Eh? I won?
You're fast!
I'm sorry.
Julia!
11 to 2.
I changed the racket to one-sided.
It was worth it.
Listen, if it was this side, you would
have won.
There must be a god of victory over
there.
It's an excuse.
I can't help it.
I lost.
I think of volleyball more than table
tennis.
I will overcome the ballet technique
and compete with table tennis.
Haru-chan is throwing the ball up.
I think she will be fine.
I will do my best to defeat her.
Next, the match between Julia and the
director, Haru-chan, will begin.
Who is the director?
Julia is in a good mood because she
changed the racket.
She is a little strong.
I will do my best to defeat her.
Hiori said that Julia's ball is fast.
She is a little scared.
She has a skill.
She is fast.
Start!
The first player, Ayaka
Nice!
I did it!
You're a little too fast!
I'm fast!
Here I go!
Ayaka's first try
See? She's fast!
Here I go!
I did it!
Ayaka's second try
You don't do this here, right?
You do it like this!
You did it like this at the beginning!
I don't know!
What's that?
That's Julia.
Here I go!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Oh! No!
Oh!
I did it!
Julia, you're amazing!
Oh, the extension!
Don't call me an extension!
I did it!
Julia, match point!
I don't think I'll be an extension
anymore.
Yay!
Please subscribe to our channel!
Juri won!
Wow!
It didn't extend!
It didn't.
It was fast.
It was a bit too fast.
A bit too fast.
Please subscribe to our channel!
I can't read her.
She's so detailed.
But she's my senior.
I can read her while I'm playing table
tennis.
I think I can.
Speaking of summer, it's IZ.
I'm talking about Uchuu again.
Her costume was blue.
It was cute.
Ice bomb.
I haven't drawn anything recently.
I'm drawing vanilla.
Please.
Vanilla.
Next, it's Banh Thio.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Ready, set, go!
Oh!
LOL
OK, next!
I'll go.
Oh!
I'm out.
LOL
You reacted like a grandpa.
I'll go.
Oh!
3 points!
This way.
Oh, no.
I'll go.
4 points.
The winner's glasses might be over
here.
5 points.
It's not rust.
It's rust.
Rust?
I'll go.
6 points!
That was fast!
7 points!
Please subscribe to our channel!
No!
I'm sorry.
This is bad.
I'll go.
I want to get one point.
I got one point!
I did it!
I'm scared!
Oh, you're right!
It's a match point for you, Anri.
Anri, you're strong.
Here I go.
Oh!
No!
Anri wins!
I don't want to play anymore!
I hate table tennis!
What should I do? My juniors are going
to beat me up.
I'm scared!
To be continued!
The winner is...
Bambi!
I did it!
Bambi is the strongest in the world.
She is young.
I did it!
How was it?
It's been a while since I played table
tennis.
It was fun.
I want to play this kind of game again.
I want to play.
I want to play with 6 people.
I think I can hit a ball.
I think so, too.
It was fun.
Is there a second game?
If there is,
let's meet at the second table tennis
tournament.
See you again.
Bye bye.
Thank you for watching.
I want to perform live with my body
full of passion.
I will definitely show you a more
powerful image than last year.
I'm really glad that SenzenBerry is
cheering for us.
Our mystery story has just begun.
I think that if everyone is together,
there is no such thing and the
possibilities are limitless.
If SenzenBerry and the members are
together, we can definitely make a big
wall into a small wall.
We believe in that.
So, please wait for us, Nakano-san and
Pura-san!
Dash! Dash! Let's chase our dreams!
Dash! Dash! Dash! A dream that will
never wake up!
If I'm with you, I can make it come
true!
I can become a Breaky!
How is it?
Do you like it?
I'm looking forward to the next live
performance.
I'm sure everyone will wear this.
Everyone will wear this.
The release date is autumn.
It's time to wear this.
Please try it on.
Good evening, everyone.
What kind of event is it today?
It's a kangaroo event.
I'm dying in August today.
Julia is growing up now.
Have you grown up?
I haven't.
What are you talking about?
I'm growing up.
Ta-da!
Close!
Here it is.
Yes.
Oharu-san.
Kangaroo event.
Oharu's pants are cute.
This is cute, isn't it?
Can you see it?
Did you see it?
Pink.
Pink pants.
Cute.
I am pink.
Hey!
Someone hold it.
Did you get the kangaroo hoodie?
Yes.
Thank you.
Please buy a lot.
Please subscribe to my channel.
Thank you for watching.
Please subscribe to our channel!